上周末  爸爸妈妈
Last weekend, Mom and Dad
去蒙特雷参加菜蓟节去了
went to the artichoke festival in Monterey.
迪兰的妈妈请缨带双胞胎
And Dylan's mom had the twins,
于是我们就趁机办了个派对
so we took the opportunity to have a little party,
就为了看看我们是否还有那个疯劲儿
just to see if we still had it in us.
果然宝刀未老
We did.
我在追踪披萨外卖哥的动态
I'm trackin' the pizza guy,
披萨外卖哥  披萨外卖哥
the pizza guy, the pizza guy!
他叫易卜拉欣
His name is Ibrahim!
别忘了带蒜香面包结  蒜香面包结
Don't forget the garlic knots, garlic knots, garlic knots!
哟  这派对真是"史棒"
Yo! This party is the GOAT.
就是"有史以来最棒的派对"
Greatest of all time.
我叫道格  是住你们家街对面的邻居
I'm Doug, your across-the-street neighbor.
我正好在倒垃圾  听到派对的声音
I was just curbin' my bins, heard the party noise,
就想着来加入你们
thought I'd join up.
要给你加点酒吗
Want a refill on that?
我是绝对不会接受你的酒的
There is no scenario where I accept a drink from you.
酷
Lit.